Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Sir Hubert Wilkins, undated; 10 (Box 1563)
    - [Alaskan people eating], 12
    - [Alaskan man with snow in his beard], 13
    - [Portrait of an Alaskan woman], 14
    - [Profile of an Alaskan man], 15
    - [A man in a fur coat], 16
    - [Two Alaskan children sitting with a woman], 17
    - [An Alaskan child], 18
    - Caption: Sir Ernest Shackleton in Polar Clothing, 19
    - [Sir Ernest Shackleton with a camera], 20
    - [Snowy mountains], 21
    - [A ship in Alaskan waters], 22
    - [Snowy mountains], 23
    - [Map of the South Pole], 24
    - [View from the derigible], 25
    - [A parade in the streets of a city], 26
    - [Aerial view of a river], 27
    - [Aerial view of a river], 28
    - [Clouds], 29
    - [Aerial view of a town], 30
    - [Man with an accordian], 31
    - [A derigible flying over a crowd], 32
    - [A man looking out a window], 33
    - [Aerial view of an icy ocean], 34
    - [Aerial view of a town], 35
    - [Aerial view of islands], 36
    - [Aerial view of farmlands], 37
    - [An island in the ocean], 38
    - [Iceburgs], 39
    - [Archway in the iceburg], 40
    - [Aerial view of the sea], 41
  - Subject files: Sir Hubert Wilkins, undated; 11 (Box 1563)
    - LT and Sir Hubert, 1
    - Verso: LT and Sir Hubert, 1-verso
    - Portrait of Sir Hubert Wilkins [3 copies], 2
    - Portrait of Sir Hubert Wilkins [3 copies], 3
  - Subject files: Sir Hubert Wilkins (photographs for use in Arctic Knight: Sir Hubert Wilkins by Lowell Thomas), circa late 1950s - 1960; 12 (Box 1563)
    - [Sir Hubert Wilkins with a camera on a boat], 1
    - [Sir Hubert Wilkins standing with a man and a woman], 2
    - [Sir Hubery Wilkins talking with a man], 3
    - [A submarine in in the Arctic (?)], 4
    - [Sir Hubery Wilkins working on a typewritter inside a submarine], 5
    - [Man standing on a ship], 6
    - [Two men on horses in the street], 7
    - "Sir Hubert Wilkins", 8
    - Verso: "Sir Hubert Wilkins", 8-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas with four other men], 9
    - Two men wokring on a propeller], 10
    - [Three people standing on a mountain overlooking a building], [2 copies], 11
    - [Two men sitting outside tipis], 12
    - [A group of men], 13
    - [Soldiers sitting in the trenches], 14
    - [Plane crash (?)], 15
    - [People on a ship waving], 16
    - [Snowy mountains], 17
    - [Two men at their campsite], 18
    - [Someone inspecting a propeller], 19
    - [Man lookinh at a map], 20
    - [Two people kissing], 21
    - [An airplane in the water, iceburg in the background], 22
    - [Men on a boat (?)], 23
    - [Man with a camera, and native Alaskans], 24
    - [Two men dressed in fur], 25
    - [People sitting outside a train], 26
    - [Men in a hot air balloon], 27
    - [Airplane in the water], 28
  - Subject files: Sir Hubert Wilkins (photographs for use in Arctic Knight: Sir Hubert Wilkins by Lowell Thomas), circa late 1950s - 1960; 13 (Box 1563)
    - Painting of Lowell Thomas of Signour[?] Wilkins, 1
    - Verso: Painting of Lowell Thomas of Signour[?] Wilkins, 1-verso
    - [Signour[?] Wilkins], 2
    - Portrait of Sir Hubert Wilkins Painted by Signour[?] Wilkins [3 copies], 3
    - Verso: Portrait of Sir Hubert Wilkins Painted by Signour[?] Wilkins, 3-verso
    - Caption: Captain Wilkin, 4
    - Caption: Love from George Cambridge, England Sept 11th 1912, 5
  - Subject files: President Woodrow Wilson, 1912 - 1915; 14 (Box 1563)
    - Our picture shows President Woodrow Wilson delivering his address at the formal opening of the American University which took place this afternoon in Washington; Feb 1915, 1
    - Verso: Our picture shows President Woodrow Wilson delivering his address at the formal opening of the American University which took place this afternoon in Washington; Feb 1915, 1-verso
    - [portrait of Woodrow Wilson], 2
  - Subject files: Admiral Worden, undated; 15 (Box 1563)
    - [Portrait of Admiral Worden], 1
  - Subject files: World War II (radio commentators tour of the war fronts), 1945; 16 (Box 1563)
    - A NINTH AIR FORCE BOMBER BASE, France---Lowell Thomas, noted war correspondent and radio commentator discusses questions of tactical air power with Major Hwang T's-Piao and Major Chen Yu-Feng (right) at a Ninth Air Force bomber base.; The correspondents, of which Mr. Thomas was a member, visited the base of the 410th Light Bombardment Group, in France, to see how the tactical air force operates. The two Chinese airmen are attached to the Ninth Air Force as observers for the Chinese Air Force, 1
    - Note: [press release] A NINTH AIR FORCE BOMBER BASE, France---Lowell Thomas, noted war correspondent and radio commentator discusses questions of tactical air power with Major Hwang T's-Piao and Major Chen Yu-Feng (right) at a Ninth Air Force bomber base.; The correspondents, of which Mr. Thomas was a member, visited the base of the 410th Light Bombardment Group, in France, to see how the tactical air force operates. The two Chinese airmen are attached to the Ninth Air Force as observers for the Chinese Air Force, 2
    - [Lowell Thomas standing in the doorway of a plane, World War II], [2 copies], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas standing in front of a plane, World War II], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas on the sidewalk during World War II], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas in a city street during World War II], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas in his military dress during World War II], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas and others outside of a plane during World War II], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas and other men in military uniform standing outside of a plane, World War II], [4 copies], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with three other military personnel, World War II], [3 copies], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas and two others, World War II], [3 copies], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas and others outside of a plane during World War II], 12
  - [Lowell Thomas and others standing on the steps to a plane, World War II], [5 copies], 1945; 17 (Box 1563)
    - 1. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Ober-Olm, Germany. 17 Apr. 1945. Mechanics working on their repair of a Mustang. Note the damaged hangars rear. This field was quickly converted after its capture, 1
    - Verso: 1. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Ober-Olm, Germany. 17 Apr. 1945. Mechanics working on their repair of a Mustang. Note the damaged hangars rear. This field was quickly converted after its capture, 1-verso
    - 2. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Gutersloh, Germany. 12 Apr. 1945. Lowell Thomas looking over damaged tail of a Thunderbolt, 2
    - Verso: 2. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Gutersloh, Germany. 12 Apr. 1945. Lowell Thomas looking over damaged tail of a Thunderbolt, 2-verso
    - 3. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Wiesbaden, Germany 15 Apr. 1945. Howard Barnes, W.O.R. & Herald Tribune Commentator and George Hamilton Combs, W.H.H. at work in their room at "Press Camp" 9th Air Force. Note painting above their heads, 3
    - Verso: 3. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Wiesbaden, Germany 15 Apr. 1945. Howard Barnes, W.O.R. & Herald Tribune Commentator and George Hamilton Combs, W.H.H. at work in their room at "Press Camp" 9th Air Force. Note painting above their heads, 3-verso
    - 4. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Ober-Olm, Germany. 17 Apr. 1945. Lt. Col. Glenn Eagleston, Alhambra, Calif., left; and Lt. Col. Jack Bradley, Brownwood, Texas, Deputy C.O. of 354th Fighter Group briefing pilots before they take off on a mission over Germany, 4
    - Verso: 4. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Ober-Olm, Germany. 17 Apr. 1945. Lt. Col. Glenn Eagleston, Alhambra, Calif., left; and Lt. Col. Jack Bradley, Brownwood, Texas, Deputy C.O. of 354th Fighter Group briefing pilots before they take off on a mission over Germany, 4-verso
    - 5. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Ober-Olm, Germany 17 Apr. 1945. Left to right: Lt. Robert Roberson, Chicago, Ill.; Capt. Gus Allen, San Angelo, Texas; Lt. Girard Kress, Williamsport, Pa., and Lt. Russell Kline, Lockwood, N.Y. checking their maps before take-off, 5
    - Verso: 5. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Ober-Olm, Germany 17 Apr. 1945. Left to right: Lt. Robert Roberson, Chicago, Ill.; Capt. Gus Allen, San Angelo, Texas; Lt. Girard Kress, Williamsport, Pa., and Lt. Russell Kline, Lockwood, N.Y. checking their maps before take-off, 5-verso
    - 6. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Ober-Olm, Germany. 17 Apr. 1945. A Thunderbolt of the 354th Fighter Group Landing at its Field in Ober-Olm, Germany, 6
    - Verso: 6. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Ober-Olm, Germany. 17 Apr. 1945. A Thunderbolt of the 354th Fighter Group Landing at its Field in Ober-Olm, Germany, 6-verso
    - 7. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Ober-Olm, Germany. 17 Apr. 1945. Fighter Pilots of the 355th Squadron just before taking off on a mission, 7
    - Verso: 7. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Ober-Olm, Germany. 17 Apr. 1945. Fighter Pilots of the 355th Squadron just before taking off on a mission, 7-verso
    - [2 copies] 8. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Ober-Olm, Germany- 17 Apr. 1945. 2nd Lt. Kenneth E. Neidigh, Salem, Kansas who was shot down March 31st. over Germany captured by Germans and put in prison. He escaped April 10th when American Forces approached prison camp. He flew with the 354th Fighter Group, 355th Squadron, 8
    - Verso: 8. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Ober-Olm, Germany- 17 Apr. 1945. 2nd Lt. Kenneth E. Neidigh, Salem, Kansas who was shot down March 31st. over Germany captured by Germans and put in prison. He escaped April 10th when American Forces approached prison camp. He flew with the 354th Fighter Group, 355th Squadron, 8-verso
    - 12. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Wiesbaden, Germany - 15 Apr. 1945. Mr. Quincy Howe, C.B.S. Radio Commentator listening in on the radio for the latest in War News, 9
    - Verso: 12. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Wiesbaden, Germany - 15 Apr. 1945. Mr. Quincy Howe, C.B.S. Radio Commentator listening in on the radio for the latest in War News, 9-verso
    - [2 copies] Verso: 14. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Wiesbaden, Germany 15 Apr. 1945. #1. Lt. Col. Leroy Gowart, MGO, of Wiesbaden, Germany with two of his guards outside his Headquarters, 10
    - Verso: 14. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Wiesbaden, Germany 15 Apr. 1945. #1. Lt. Col. Leroy Gowart, MGO, of Wiesbaden, Germany with two of his guards outside his Headquarters, 10-verso
    - 14. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Wiesbaden, Germany 15 Apr. 1945. #2. Lt. Col. Leroy Gowart, Center, talking to Quincy Howe, C.B.S. left; and Howard Barnes, W.O.R. and Herald Tribune, right, 11
    - Verso: 14. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Wiesbaden, Germany 15 Apr. 1945. #2. Lt. Col. Leroy Gowart, Center, talking to Quincy Howe, C.B.S. left; and Howard Barnes, W.O.R. and Herald Tribune, right, 11-verso
    - 15. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany, 10 Apr. 1945. Harold Schoessler, of Ritzville, Washington, on guard in doorway of Town Major's Hqts. In Cologne. Note ruins in rear. Town Major located on Kaiser Wilhelm-ring, Cologne, 12
    - Verso: 15. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany, 10 Apr. 1945. Harold Schoessler, of Ritzville, Washington, on guard in doorway of Town Major's Hqts. In Cologne. Note ruins in rear. Town Major located on Kaiser Wilhelm-ring, Cologne, 12-verso
    - 16. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Wiesbaden, Germany. 15th Apr. 1945. Major Benjamin Wright, PRO of 9th AAF Press Camp on left, looking out of window of headquarters in Wiesbaden with the rest of the members of his staff, 13
    - Verso: 16. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Wiesbaden, Germany. 15th Apr. 1945. Major Benjamin Wright, PRO of 9th AAF Press Camp on left, looking out of window of headquarters in Wiesbaden with the rest of the members of his staff, 13-verso
    - 17. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Juvencourt Airfield, France. 11 Apr. 1945. Major Gen. Sam Anderson Commanding the 9th Bombardment Division talking to crew members just after returning from mission of bombing Ordnance Dept at Nuremburg, 14
    - Verso: 17. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Juvencourt Airfield, France. 11 Apr. 1945. Major Gen. Sam Anderson Commanding the 9th Bombardment Division talking to crew members just after returning from mission of bombing Ordnance Dept at Nuremburg, 14-verso
    - 18. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Juvencourt Airfield, France. 11 Apr. 1945. Members of the ground crews of the 9th Bombardment Division of Juvencourt Airfield pushing one of the bombers in proper parking space after returning from a mission, 15
    - Verso: 18. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Juvencourt Airfield, France. 11 Apr. 1945. Members of the ground crews of the 9th Bombardment Division of Juvencourt Airfield pushing one of the bombers in proper parking space after returning from a mission, 15-verso
    - [2 copies] 20. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Juvencourt Airfield, France. 11 Apr. 1945. Some of the ground crew reading the first news on the late President Roosevelt's death, 16
    - Verso: 20. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Juvencourt Airfield, France. 11 Apr. 1945. Some of the ground crew reading the first news on the late President Roosevelt's death, 16-verso
    - 21. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Juvencourt Airfield, France. 11 Apr. 1945. A-20s "Peeling off" before landing, 17
    - Verso: 21. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Juvencourt Airfield, France. 11 Apr. 1945. A-20s "Peeling off" before landing, 17-verso
    - [2 copies] 23. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Juvencourt Airfield, France. 11 Apr. 1945. L. to R. Quincy Howe, CBS; Lowell Thomas, NBC; Maj. Gen. Sam Anderson, Commanding Gen. 9th Bombardment Division Pointing; Howard Barnes, WOR; Col. Robert Hughey. C.O. Juvencourt Airfield; and right, George Hamilton Combs, WHN, 18
    - Verso: 23. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Juvencourt Airfield, France. 11 Apr. 1945. L. to R. Quincy Howe, CBS; Lowell Thomas, NBC; Maj. Gen. Sam Anderson, Commanding Gen. 9th Bombardment Division Pointing; Howard Barnes, WOR; Col. Robert Hughey. C.O. Juvencourt Airfield; and right, George Hamilton Combs, WHN, 18-verso
    - 24. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Juvencourt Airfield, France. 11 Apr. 1945. Maj. Gen. Sam Anderson, Commanding General 9th Bombardment Division of the 9th Air Force left and Brig. Gen. Edwin J. Backus, Commanding General 97th Wing of 9th Air Force, 19
    - Verso: 24. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Juvencourt Airfield, France. 11 Apr. 1945. Maj. Gen. Sam Anderson, Commanding General 9th Bombardment Division of the 9th Air Force left and Brig. Gen. Edwin J. Backus, Commanding General 97th Wing of 9th Air Force, 19-verso
    - [2 copies] 25. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Juvencourt Airfield, France. 11 Apr. 1945. Group of A-20 bombers "Peeling off" on returning from their mission of bombing an ordnance depot at Nuremburg, 20
    - Verso: 25. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Juvencourt Airfield, France. 11 Apr. 1945. Group of A-20 bombers "Peeling off" on returning from their mission of bombing an ordnance depot at Nuremburg, 20-verso
    - 26. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Juvencourt Airfield, France. 11 Apr. 1945. Group of A-20 bombers "peeling off" on returning from their mission of bombing an ordnance depot at Nuremburg, 21
    - Verso: 26. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Juvencourt Airfield, France. 11 Apr. 1945. Group of A-20 bombers "peeling off" on returning from their mission of bombing an ordnance depot at Nuremburg, 21-verso
    - 27. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Florence, Italy. 28 Apr. 1945. Italian civilian workmen, with British engineers, constructing a Bailey Bridge across the Arno River. Three out of 4 bridges spanning the Arno River were destroyed by the retreating Germans. They left only the world famous Ponte Vecchio bridge which was first built of wood in the year 996, 22
    - Verso: 27. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Florence, Italy. 28 Apr. 1945. Italian civilian workmen, with British engineers, constructing a Bailey Bridge across the Arno River. Three out of 4 bridges spanning the Arno River were destroyed by the retreating Germans. They left only the world famous Ponte Vecchio bridge which was first built of wood in the year 996, 22-verso
    - 28. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Vatican City, Rome, Italy 30 Apr. 1945. His Holiness, the Pope, talking to his audience of Soldiers, Sailors, Wacs, Waves, Wrens, Allied Soldiers, Etc., 23
    - Verso: 28. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Vatican City, Rome, Italy 30 Apr. 1945. His Holiness, the Pope, talking to his audience of Soldiers, Sailors, Wacs, Waves, Wrens, Allied Soldiers, Etc., 23-verso
    - [2 copies] 29. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Vatican City, Rome, Italy. 30 Apr. 1945. His Holiness, the Pope, blessing the crowd of Allied soldiers, Wacs, Wrens, etc., at the daily audience in the Vatican, 24
    - Verso: 29. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Vatican City, Rome, Italy. 30 Apr. 1945. His Holiness, the Pope, blessing the crowd of Allied soldiers, Wacs, Wrens, etc., at the daily audience in the Vatican, 24-verso
    - 30. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Mainz, Germany 23-28 Apr. 1945. Italian civilians crossing the world famous Ponte Vecchio bridge first built of wood in 996, and later was rebuilt in stone. There are stores on each side of the bridge, 25
    - Verso: 30. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Mainz, Germany 23-28 Apr. 1945. Italian civilians crossing the world famous Ponte Vecchio bridge first built of wood in 996, and later was rebuilt in stone. There are stores on each side of the bridge, 25-verso
    - [2 copies] 31. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Vatican City, Rome, Italy. 30 Apr. 1945. Lt. and Mrs. Frank Ursino, of 2449 Irving Place, Seattle, Washington, just after they received the Pope's Blessing. The bride was known as the "Belle of Rome", 26
    - Verso: 31. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Vatican City, Rome, Italy. 30 Apr. 1945. Lt. and Mrs. Frank Ursino, of 2449 Irving Place, Seattle, Washington, just after they received the Pope's Blessing. The bride was known as the "Belle of Rome", 26-verso
    - 32. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany 19 Apr. 1945. Gen. George S. Patton, Jr., standing in front of Headquarters, in Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany, holding a giant shot-gun acquired during his travels through Germany, 27
    - Verso: 32. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany 19 Apr. 1945. Gen. George S. Patton, Jr., standing in front of Headquarters, in Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany, holding a giant shot-gun acquired during his travels through Germany, 27-verso
    - 33. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany. 19 Apr. 1945. Gen. George S. Patton, Jr. leaving his Headquarters with Lowell Thomas, NBC Radio Commentator, 28
    - Verso: 33. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany. 19 Apr. 1945. Gen. George S. Patton, Jr. leaving his Headquarters with Lowell Thomas, NBC Radio Commentator, 28-verso
    - 34. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany. 19 Apr. 1945. General George S. Patton, Jr. and Maj. Gen. O.P. Weyland standing in front of Pattons' headquarters in Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany, 29
    - Verso: 34. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany. 19 Apr. 1945. General George S. Patton, Jr. and Maj. Gen. O.P. Weyland standing in front of Pattons' headquarters in Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany, 29-verso
    - 35. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany. 19 Apr. 1945. L. to R.; Gen. George S. Patton, Jr.; Maj. Gen. O.P. Weyland of the 9th Air Force; George Hamilton Combs, W.H.N. and Lowell Thomas, N.B.C.'s Radio Commentator, 30
    - Verso: 35. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Hershfeld [Hirschfeld?], Germany. 19 Apr. 1945. L. to R.; Gen. George S. Patton, Jr.; Maj. Gen. O.P. Weyland of the 9th Air Force; George Hamilton Combs, W.H.N. and Lowell Thomas, N.B.C.'s Radio Commentator, 30-verso
    - 36. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany 10 Apr. 1945. Cesar Saerchinger, N.B.C. standing near chimney with smoke coming out indicating the basement of the "Deutche Bank" is being used for business as usual. The rest of the building is completely destroyed except for the basement, 31
    - Verso: 36. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany 10 Apr. 1945. Cesar Saerchinger, N.B.C. standing near chimney with smoke coming out indicating the basement of the "Deutche Bank" is being used for business as usual. The rest of the building is completely destroyed except for the basement, 31-verso
    - 37. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany. 10 Apr. 1945. 2nd Lt. William "Doc" Dougherty, and John W. Vandercook, N.B.C. on steps of Cologne Cathedral, 32
    - Verso: 37. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany. 10 Apr. 1945. 2nd Lt. William "Doc" Dougherty, and John W. Vandercook, N.B.C. on steps of Cologne Cathedral, 32-verso
    - 38. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany 10 Apr. 1945. Some of the members of party walking down a street in Cologne, Germany. Note the terrific damage from American 9th Air Force bombers, 33
    - Verso: 38. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany 10 Apr. 1945. Some of the members of party walking down a street in Cologne, Germany. Note the terrific damage from American 9th Air Force bombers, 33-verso
    - [2 copies] 39. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany. 10 Apr. 1945. 3 "Airborne" G.I.'s walking in ruined Cologne. Note Cathedral in rear. L. to R.; Pfc. Charles P. Watts, of Port Royal, Va. Pfc. T.M. Bizzuti, Detroit, Mich. Pfc. Robert Hawekotte, Chicago, Ill. All three are from the 82nd Airborne, 325th Glider regiment now stationed in Cologne, Germany, 34
    - Verso: 39. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany. 10 Apr. 1945. 3 "Airborne" G.I.'s walking in ruined Cologne. Note Cathedral in rear. L. to R.; Pfc. Charles P. Watts, of Port Royal, Va. Pfc. T.M. Bizzuti, Detroit, Mich. Pfc. Robert Hawekotte, Chicago, Ill. All three are from the 82nd Airborne, 325th Glider regiment now stationed in Cologne, Germany, 34-verso
    - 40. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany. 10 Apr. 1945. Pieces of buildings strewn over a street in Cologne, Germany the result of bombing by the 9th Air Force, 35
    - Verso: 40. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany. 10 Apr. 1945. Pieces of buildings strewn over a street in Cologne, Germany the result of bombing by the 9th Air Force, 35-verso
    - 41. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Colonge Germany. 10 Apr. 1945. Results of bombing by the 9th Air Force. Cologne, Germany, 36
    - Verso: 41. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Colonge Germany. 10 Apr. 1945. Results of bombing by the 9th Air Force. Cologne, Germany, 36-verso
    - 42. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany. 10 Apr. 1945. Cesar Saerchinger, N.B.C. and Quincy Howe, C.B.S. walking in bombed street in Cologne, Germany, 37
    - Verso: 42. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany. 10 Apr. 1945. Cesar Saerchinger, N.B.C. and Quincy Howe, C.B.S. walking in bombed street in Cologne, Germany, 37-verso
  Box 1564
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: World War II (radio commentators tour of the war fronts), 1945; 1 (Box 1564)
    - 43. Radio Commentators Tour War Fronts. Cologne, Germany 10 Apr. 1945. German civilians in line waiting outside "Town Major's Hqts" on "Kaiser-Wilhelm-Ring" strasse, in Cologne, Germany, 1